{
	"categories" : [
		{
			"category" : "german verbs",
			"questions" : [
				{
					"question" : "tanzen",
					"correct" : "to dance",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to take",
						"to drive",
						"to run"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "meinen",
					"correct" : "to think, mean",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to feel",
						"to give (to someone)",
						"to taste"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "gefallen",
					"correct" : "to be pleasing, like",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to wish",
						"to desire",
						"to fall"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "spielen",
					"correct" : "to play",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to spill",
						"to be",
						"to dance"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "nehmen",
					"correct" : "to take",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to participate",
						"to name",
						"to know"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "treten",
					"correct" : "to step",
					"incorrect" : [
						"to fall",
						"to treat (to something)",
						"to take (something)"
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"category" : "orchestral instruments",
			"questions" : [
				{
					"question" : "Which of the following is not a brass instrument?",
					"correct" : "Bassoon",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Trumpet",
						"French Horn",
						"Cornet"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "Which of these percussion instruments is not played with mallets?",
					"correct" : "Claves",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Timpani",
						"Glockenspiel",
						"Marimba"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "Which of the following instruments isn't typically valved?",
					"correct" : "Trombone",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Tuba",
						"French Horn",
						"Trumpet"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "Which of the following is not a double reed instrument?",
					"correct" : "Bass Clarinet",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Bassoon",
						"Oboe",
						"English Horn"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "Which of the following string instruments is not traditionally an orchestral instrument?",
					"correct" : "Lute",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Double Bass",
						"Viola",
						"Harp"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "From what material are the strings of stringed instrument bows typically made?",
					"correct" : "Horse hair",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Nylon",
						"Cotton",
						"Hemp"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "Which of the following drums is not typically played with a bare hand?",
					"correct" : "Snare drum",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Tambourine",
						"Conga drum",
						"Bongo drum"
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"category" : "sports rules",
			"questions" : [
				{
					"question" : "In American Football, how many points is a safety worth?",
					"correct" : "2",
					"incorrect" : [
						"6",
						"7",
						"1"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "In soccer (football), what is the restart after an offside violation?",
					"correct" : "Indirect freekick",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Direct freekick",
						"Penalty kick",
						"Goal kick"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "In volleyball, how many hits are allowed on a side before the ball is played over the net?",
					"correct" : "3",
					"incorrect" : [
						"4",
						"2",
						"5"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "In baseball, in which of the following situations could the infield fly rule apply?",
					"correct" : "Runners on first, second, and third; one out",
					"incorrect" : [
						"Runners on first, second, and third; two outs",
						"Runners on first and third; no outs",
						"Runner on second; one out"
					]
				},
				{
					"question" : "In basketball (NBA rules), how many personal fouls can you accumulate without getting disqualified?",
					"correct" : "5",
					"incorrect" : [
						"6",
						"7",
						"4"
					]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}